miniso-au.com 2018-03-15

# Miniso-au.com Privacy Statement - MINISO Australia

MINISO has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We collect certain types of information about the visitors and customers via this website, you should fully understand our policies surrounding the collection and the use of information. 

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

1.       PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED 

MINISO and Miniso-au.com offers a variety of services that are collectively referred to as the “Service”. MINISO and Miniso-au.com collect information from individuals who visit this website (“visitors”).

Some information Visitors provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions such as contacting our customer service department via e-mail, participating in our message boards or forums, e-mails to a friend, submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, registering on our website, placing orders and participating in polls, surveys and sweepstakes, we may use your current location to help to find you the nearest store. We may also combine information you give us online with other information wobtain from sources, transactions and communications. This may include, but is not limited to, data from online marketing, mobile marketing and direct mail. We may also combine this information with data that is publicly available and from other data we receive from reputable sources. This may include, but is not limited to, postal address updates and demographic data.  All data combined and stored with the on-line data is protected by this Privacy Policy. Billing and collection functions are handled by PayPal. In performing these services, PayPal collects personal information. Please see PayPal’s privacy statements on its website for details on how PayPal treats this information.

(A)    Registration 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address basically. And you may complete your information in profile fields after registering successfully , the profile fields includes but not limit to your name, country, city, gender, age, au case size, favor colors, birthday, method to buy or other details to help us know you better. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

(B)    Newsletter

Visitors can voluntarily subscribe to our newsletter by entering the email address. We will send the brand update, newest events and the monthly theme email to the subscribers. Visitors may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

(C)    Surveys 

Sometimes MINISO and Miniso-au.com posts optional surveys in which we ask visitors for demographic information (like their ages, or income level). This allows us to better target our content to our audience. We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about MINISO. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Visitors may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. You do not have to answer these surveys or all the fields in surveys. If we are asking for optional information, we will mark the required information with an asterisk (*) so you know the unmarked fields are optional and you can skip them if you want. We use the aggregated demographic information to improve the product and service, and as advertisements guideline. 

(D)    Contest and Sweepstakes

MINISO sometimes holds contest and sweepstakes in which we ask for some contact information like the email address, the demographic information like the age, gender and job, and customized information like preferred colors, preferred au case size. In some case visitors may be asked to fill out a brief survey or upload a photo, which are not limited, to exchange for allowing such visitor to enter the contest or sweepstakes. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and to notify you if you are a winner. Visitors may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. Any sweepstakes and other contests will be subject to special rules which will be identified on this website.

(E)     Other Information 

(a)     Website Navigational Information

As you navigate the www.Miniso-au.com web site, we may also collect information through the use of commonly used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons (“Website Navigational Information”). Website Navigational Information includes standard information from your web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the website (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked).

(b)     Tracking by Search Terms

MINISO tracks the searching terms which visitors enter in the searching box. The tracking is not associated with individuals, as we do not track how many pages a specific visitor looks through. We use this information to find out which areas of our website visitors like and don’t like based on the amount of traffic to those pages. This provides the basis how we arrange modify the content. 

(c)     Third party behavioral tracking

It's important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking such as Google Analytics. However, we will not use individuals’ information but the aggregate information to improve our website and service, which is stated below. 

2.       USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

Miniso uses data about Miniso-au.com visitors to perform the services requested. For example, if you subscribe to the newsletter on site, MINISO will use the information provided to send you the newsletter. 

MINISO may use the information we collect for marketing purpose. For example, MINISO will use the email you provide to send you surveys so that we can know your recent opinions on the au design and our service. And also, we may send you information about promotions or events. We are conducting with the following purpose. 

(A)    To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

(B)    To improve our website in order to serve you better.

(C)    To improve service in responding to your customer service requests.

(D)    To quickly process your transactions.

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form finish a polling, enter a contest, enter a sweepstakes, search keywords or enter information on our site.

MINISO and Miniso-au.com uses website navigational information to operate and improve the website content and optimize the website structure. We may also use website navigational information in combination with data about MINISO to provide personalized information about Miniso. And we may share aggregate information about our visitors with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. For example, we might divide Miniso-au.com’s visitors into various age groups by percentage. This data is used to customize Miniso-au.com’s content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our visitors. In no event will MINISO share individual identifying information about such user with any third party except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

(A) We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MINISO under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help MINISO and Miniso-au.com to communicate with you about offers from MINISO and Miniso-au.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

(B) We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 

(C) We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MINISO and Miniso-au.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; 

(D) We transfer information about you if MINISO and Miniso-au.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MINISO and Miniso-au.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

3.       ANTI-SPAM 

We comply with laws and gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them.

We collect your email address in order to:

(A)    Respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

(B)    Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

(C)    Send you additional information related to your product and/or service.

(D)    Continue to send emails after the original transaction has occurred

(E)     Market to our mailing list and send promotional information, surveys and other marketing events. 

We also agree to the following in sending emails:

(A)    NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses

(B)    Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly

(C)    Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of the promotional email

4.       WEBSITE NAVIGATIONAL INFORMATION

As stated above, MINISO and Miniso-au.com uses commonly used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons, to collect information as you navigate the website (“Website Navigational Information”). This section describes the types of Website Navigational Information MINISO may collect and how MINISO may use this information.

(A)    IP Addresses

An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a number that is automatically given to your computer when you surf the web. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.  MINISO and Miniso-au.com collects IP addresses for the purpose of system administration and to provide aggregate data to advertisers about the volume of use on Miniso-au.com. MINISO and Miniso-au.com does not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms and conditions or to protect our service, site, visitors, or others. 

(B)     Cookies

We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. A cookie is a small data file that transfers to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. We use cookies for several purposes, which include helping remember and process the items in the shopping cart. Understand and save user's preferences for future visits. Keep track of advertisements. Updating our site based on data such as the total number of visitors and pages viewed. Unless you choose to identify yourself to Miniso-au.com, either by responding to a promotional offer, or filling out your information such as registering with your email address, you remain anonymous to us. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this website.

5.       THIRD PARTY LINKS

This site may contain links to other sites. For example, if you “click” on a banner retailer, the “click” will take you off the Miniso-au.com site and onto other web sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Please remember whenever you give our information online, the information can be collected by unknown people. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

6.       SECURITY

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no computer security system can be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, MINISO and Miniso-au.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once MINISO and Miniso-au.com receive your transmission, MINISO and Miniso-au.com will use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. 

7.       COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

8.       CHOICE/OPT-OUT

MINISO and Miniso-au.com offers visitors the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

Visitors have the option of removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service by sending an email to feedback@miniso-au.com. Visitors may opt-out of participating in certain interactive areas (such as participation in on-line shopping or sweepstakes).

9.       MODIFING YOUR INFORMATION

If you need to change or modify information that you previously provided, please modify your information in your account’s profile. In some circumstances when you failed to do so, please send us your update at feedback@miniso-au.com.

10.   THIRD PARTY DISCLOSURE 

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

11.   DATA PROTECTION

In order to protect visitor’s data, we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur. We will notify the users via email within 2 business days, and we will notify the users via in site notification within 1 business day。

12.   FRAUD PROTECTION

We make every effort to ensure that your transaction in safe and secure. If we receive orders that are suspicious, we will try to contact you though email to verify these orders and protect unauthorized use of your account. We realize that this may cause a delay for Priority Orders if the information cannot be verified within 24 hours, however, this is for your protection. If we do not hear back from you within five business days of our email request, your order will be cancelled. MINISO and Miniso-au.com reserves the right to cancel any order that we suspect to be suspicious or fraudulent. We are committed to providing our customers with the highest level of customer service possible as well as a positive shopping experience.

13.   ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

By using this site, you signify your agreement to MINISO’S Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy or our terms and conditions, please do not use our site. MINISO and Miniso-au.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check the Privacy Policy periodically.

14.   TERMS AND CONDICITONS

Please also visit MINISO’s terms and conditions establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the entire Miniso-au.com web site.

15.   CONTACTING THE WEBSITE 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, you can support@Miniso-au.com        

Most recent amendment: January 6, 2016

© 2017 MINISO Australia. All rights reserved.
